ABC Fashion Limited

a house of apparels solution!

Office: Confidence tower -2, Flat #8B Progoti Soroni, Shahjadpur Gulshan, Dhaka-1212, Bangladesh. Tel: +88029886968

Website: www.abcfashionbd

Biography of

Ahsan Habib, Managing Director

Contact Address

: KA-71/2 (5th floor) flat# 5, Ajmari Adore,

Shajadpur, Gulsahan

Dhaka-1212

: 01714000000 Mob

E-mail : habib@abcfashionbd.com

Career Summary:

I have been continuing for 19 Years in the Readymade Garments (RMG) Sector . Mentioned below are details.

Mar -2012 – Continue	Managing director/CEO ABC Fashion Limited. (Local Buying House) Confidence center, Tower-2 Flat-8B, Shajadpur, Guslshan, Dhaka-1212
Jan -2010 - Nov-2011 (1 Years+11 Months)	Merchandising Manager LXP Export . (Indian Buying House) House#358 (5 th floor) ,Road#5(east Side) ,DOHS Baridhara , Dhaka
Oct -2008 – Dec -2009 (1 Years+2 Months)	Sr. Merchandiser Theetex Fashion Pool Ltd. House#14(2 nd and 4 th Floor) Road #06, Section 01 Uttara, Dhaka 1230, Bangladesh.
May 2006 – Aug 2008 (2 Years + 3 Months)	Sr. Merchandiser Fashion Express Ltd. H #3, R#257(3 rd /F) DOHS Baridhara ,Dhaka- 1206
Feb 2002 – Mar 2006 (4 Years)	Merchandiser Prestige Global Co. Pte. Ltd. [USA Liaison office] House # B109, Road# 8, DOHS Mohakhali, Dhaka
Feb 2000 - Jan 2002 (2 Years)	Assistance Merchandiser Crossline Bangladesh ltd, [Frances Buying House.] Banani, Dhaka

Academic Qualification :

M. COM. (Major in Marketing) 1998

National University at Dhaka College, Dhaka . * 2ND Class

ABC Fashion Limited

a house of apparels solution!

Office:

Confidence tower -2 , Flat # 8B Progoti Soroni, Shahjadpur Gulshan , Dhaka -1212, Bangladesh.

Tel: +88029886968

Website; www.abcfashionbd.com

1996

B.COM (Major in Accounting and Marketing)

National University at Rajbari Govt. College .

* 3rd Class

1994

H.S.C. (Major in Accounting and Marketing with English)

Rajbari Govt. College .

* 2ND Class

1991

S.S.C. (Major in Mathematic, Biology & Chemistry.)

Ramdia BMBC high school, Rajbari.

* 2ND Class

Country visited:

Hong Kong

- India
- Thailand
- Malaysia
- Germany
- Poland
- France
- Italy
- Spain
- Swaziland

Personal profile:

Father's Name: Late Joydar Sheakh Mother's Name: Mrs Khadeza Begum

Date of Birth : 05 July 1975

Marital status : Married Religion : Islam (sunny)

Nationality : Bangladeshi (by birth)

Permanent Address: Village : Horikol,

nanent Address: vinage , riorikoi,

Post : Ramdia,

Thana : Baliakandi, District : Rajbari, Bangladesh

Yours faithfully,

Ahaan Halob Mnaging Director ABC Fushion Ltd.